Guide to the Royal Development Company (Trinity Mine) Records 1896-1946
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Maps, Plans and Oversized Materials, 1896-1930; Series V
  - Plans, 1896-1930; Subseries 2
    - Mill Transformer Station, 1930 May 29 (Folder-drawing 8/7)
    - Plan of Power House (James Creek Power Project), 1923 April 28 (Folder-drawing 8/8)
    - Power House Extension, 1928 August 1 (Folder-drawing 8/9)
    - Force Diagram of Floatation Roof, undated (Folder-drawing 8/10)
    - Proposed School Building, undated (Folder-drawing 8/11)
    - School House, 1929 September 4 (Folder-drawing 8/12)
    - Plan of Store House, 1923 May 2 (Folder-drawing 8/13)
    - Front Elevation (unidentified building), undated (Folder-drawing 8/14)
    - Plan of Family House in Respect to Lot, 1929 August 26 (Folder-drawing 8/15)
    - Elevation of End of Crushing Building, undated (Folder-drawing 8/16)
    - Plan of unidentified building, undated (Folder-drawing 8/16)
    - Proposed camp residence, undated (Folder-drawing 8/17)
    - unidentified drawing, undated (Folder-drawing 8/17)
    - Plan of unidentified building (Conveyor systems), undated (Folder-drawing 8/18)
    - Plan of Mueller Hood Furnace system (3 pages), undated (Folder-drawing 8/19)
    - Force Diagram of Fine Grinding Section (Fragile), undated (Folder-drawing 8/20)
    - Coarse Ore Bin (fragment - fragile), undated (Folder-drawing 8/21)
    - Marcy Ball Mill (fragment - fragile), undated (Folder-drawing 8/22)
    - Plan of unidentified machinery (“#629”), undated (Folder-drawing 8/23)
    - Section drawing of unidentified building, undated (Folder-drawing 8/24)
    - Plan of unidentified building, undated (Folder-drawing 8/25)
    - Unidentified Plans, undated (Folder-drawing 8/26 - 8/31)
    - Unidentified Plans (fragments), undated (Folder-drawing 8/32 - 8/34)
  - Oversize Material, 1929-1930; Subseries 3
    - Royal Development Company Trinity Camp Organizational Chart, Undated (Folder-item 9/1)
    - Daily Report Trinity Tunnel Operations, 1929 (Folder-item 9/2)
    - Daily Report Trinity Tunnel Operations, 1930 January (Folder-item 9/3)
    - Daily Report Trinity Tunnel Operations, 1930 February (Folder-item 9/4)